Amber	B-PERSON
Walker	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Christopherside	B-LOCATION
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

midnight:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Joseph	B-PERSON
Elliott	B-PERSON
transporting	O
IED	B-WEAPON
through	O
Kimmouth.	B-LOCATION

At	O
03:00,	B-TIME
James	B-PERSON
Harris	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Barbara	B-PERSON
Wood	B-PERSON
in	O
Lake	O
Brittanyland	O
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

Madison	B-PERSON
Fischer	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
West	O
Bobbymouth	O
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
Edward	B-PERSON
Mitchell	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Paul	B-PERSON
Roberts	B-PERSON
in	O
Jenniferchester	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
grenade.	B-WEAPON

At	O
13:30,	B-TIME
Jessica	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Jessica	B-PERSON
Sanders	B-PERSON
in	O
South	O
Jeremyberg	O
to	O
discuss	O
drone.	B-WEAPON

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Port	O
Stephenland	O
just	O
after	O
20:15.	B-TIME

13:30:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Susan	B-PERSON
York	B-PERSON
transporting	O
IED	B-WEAPON
through	O
West	O
Eric.	O

Julie	B-PERSON
Phillips	B-PERSON
and	O
Melissa	B-PERSON
Potter	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
drone	B-WEAPON
near	O
Ortegafurt	B-LOCATION
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

At	O
13:30,	B-TIME
Annette	B-PERSON
Williams	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Joann	B-PERSON
Murphy	B-PERSON
in	O
Thompsonfurt	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
AK-47.	B-WEAPON

Authorities	O
in	O
Henrytown	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Kimberly	B-PERSON
Jones	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Dr.	B-PERSON
Bruce	O
Hart	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Silvaport	B-LOCATION
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

midnight:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Michelle	B-PERSON
Lee	B-PERSON
transporting	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
through	O
Port	O
Angela.	O

Allen	B-PERSON
Wilson	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
South	O
Michaelburgh	O
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
IED	B-WEAPON
in	O
South	O
Sarahview	O
led	O
by	O
Melissa	B-PERSON
Clayton	B-PERSON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Mrs.	B-PERSON
Stephanie	O
Hayden	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Lake	O
Katelyn	O
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
drone	B-WEAPON
in	O
Francisstad	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Marcus	B-PERSON
Morris	B-PERSON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Nicole	B-PERSON
Davidson	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Rebeccafurt	B-LOCATION
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

midnight:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Isaac	B-PERSON
Beard	B-PERSON
transporting	O
drone	B-WEAPON
through	O
Amyton.	B-LOCATION

midnight:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Robert	B-PERSON
Edwards	B-PERSON
transporting	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
through	O
East	O
Robert.	B-PERSON

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Gina	B-PERSON
Steele	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Toddside	B-LOCATION
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

At	O
13:30,	B-TIME
Nancy	B-PERSON
Parsons	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Justin	B-PERSON
Taylor	B-PERSON
in	O
East	O
Sandra	O
to	O
discuss	O
RPG.	B-WEAPON

Peter	B-PERSON
Oneal	O
MD	B-PERSON
and	O
Robert	B-PERSON
Shields	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
near	O
Watsonhaven	B-LOCATION
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
Geraldton	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Nicole	B-PERSON
Howard	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
East	O
Cherylburgh	O
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Donald	B-PERSON
Vasquez	B-PERSON
transporting	O
IED	B-WEAPON
through	O
Washingtonbury.	B-LOCATION

Authorities	O
in	O
West	O
Rebeccaville	O
detained	O
Brittany	B-PERSON
White	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Jonathan	B-PERSON
Wise	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
New	O
Douglas	O
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

At	O
midnight,	B-TIME
Caitlin	B-PERSON
Stewart	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Sierra	B-PERSON
Mitchell	B-PERSON
in	O
Lisaville	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
sniper	O
rifle.	O

dawn:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Megan	B-PERSON
Clayton	B-PERSON
transporting	O
chemical	O
gas	O
through	O
North	O
Nancyhaven.	O

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
New	O
Crystaltown	O
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

13:30:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Karen	B-PERSON
Jones	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
North	O
Thomas.	O

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Connor	B-PERSON
Willis	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Lydiamouth.	B-LOCATION

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
chemical	O
gas	O
spotted	O
near	O
North	O
Ericaton	O
just	O
after	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	B-WEAPON
carrying	O
drone	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Thompsonview	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Austin	B-PERSON
Hood	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
South	O
Sabrina	O
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Walterchester	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
20:15.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Jennifer	B-PERSON
Williams	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Danieltown.	B-LOCATION

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Sarah	B-PERSON
Delacruz	B-PERSON
transporting	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
through	O
Ericburgh.	B-LOCATION

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Rhonda	B-PERSON
Simon	B-PERSON
transporting	O
chemical	O
gas	O
through	O
East	O
Stephanieland.	O

Steven	B-PERSON
Sanford	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
North	O
Joel	O
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

At	O
midnight,	B-TIME
Candace	B-PERSON
Leon	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Debra	B-PERSON
Ramos	B-PERSON
in	O
Tamaraland	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
AK-47.	B-WEAPON

Authorities	O
in	O
Duartemouth	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Anthony	B-PERSON
Holmes	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
Hernandezshire	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
13:30.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Angelica	B-PERSON
Lopez	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
West	O
Benjamin.	O

dawn:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Alexandria	B-PERSON
Valdez	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
Greenetown.	B-LOCATION

Dakota	B-PERSON
Wilson	B-PERSON
and	O
Jon	B-PERSON
Vargas	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
drone	B-WEAPON
near	O
Yangmouth	B-LOCATION
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
IED	B-WEAPON
in	O
North	O
Cameron	O
led	O
by	O
Jennifer	B-PERSON
Walker	B-PERSON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
IED	B-WEAPON
in	O
Smithhaven	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Dawn	B-PERSON
Bowen	B-PERSON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

03:00:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Joseph	B-PERSON
Cantrell	B-PERSON
transporting	O
IED	B-WEAPON
through	O
East	O
Suzanne.	O

Jessica	B-PERSON
Anderson	B-PERSON
and	O
Kelly	B-PERSON
Wilson	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
near	O
Keithbury	B-LOCATION
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Jeffrey	B-PERSON
Rodriguez	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Brownchester	B-LOCATION
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
North	O
Robert	O
just	O
after	O
13:30.	B-TIME

At	O
03:00,	B-TIME
Mark	B-PERSON
Jacobs	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
William	B-PERSON
Schultz	B-PERSON
in	O
Galvanstad	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
drone.	B-WEAPON

Authorities	O
in	O
South	O
Mercedesberg	O
detained	O
Olivia	B-PERSON
Allen	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
Lake	O
Jamieview	O
just	O
after	O
evening.	B-TIME

Steven	B-PERSON
Ball	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Port	O
Roberto	O
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
IED	B-WEAPON
in	O
Tammyhaven	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Jennifer	B-PERSON
Tapia	B-PERSON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
North	O
Paulfurt	O
led	O
by	O
Steven	B-PERSON
Armstrong	B-PERSON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Raymond	B-PERSON
Alexander	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Hughesburgh	B-LOCATION
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
Stevenborough	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Timothy	B-PERSON
Nguyen	B-PERSON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Port	O
Christopher	O
detained	O
Bradley	B-PERSON
Bradley	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Wandatown	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Kathleen	B-PERSON
Cole	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

dawn:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Kevin	B-PERSON
Barnes	B-PERSON
transporting	O
drone	B-WEAPON
through	O
Johnstonville.	B-LOCATION

Robin	B-PERSON
Mitchell	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Billyborough	B-LOCATION
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

07:45:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Mary	B-PERSON
Scott	B-PERSON
transporting	O
chemical	O
gas	O
through	O
Angelaberg.	B-LOCATION

Jeremy	B-PERSON
Gray	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Thomaschester	B-LOCATION
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
in	O
West	O
Alexander	O
led	O
by	O
Anthony	B-PERSON
Mitchell	B-PERSON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

03:00:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Nicole	B-PERSON
Evans	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
Smithstad.	B-LOCATION

20:15:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Timothy	B-PERSON
Miller	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
Davenportstad.	B-LOCATION

Brittany	B-PERSON
Gross	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Port	O
Davidburgh	O
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Cynthia	B-PERSON
Leonard	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
East	O
Dustin	O
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Port	O
Williamfurt	O
detained	O
Wesley	B-PERSON
Raymond	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
New	O
David	B-PERSON
detained	O
Benjamin	B-PERSON
Young	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Port	O
Caitlin	O
detained	O
Natasha	B-PERSON
Walsh	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Jacqueline	B-PERSON
Wilson	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
drone	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
East	O
Jacobshire.	O

Authorities	O
in	O
South	O
Williamton	O
detained	O
Deborah	B-PERSON
Baker	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Noah	B-PERSON
Castaneda	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Amyshire	B-LOCATION
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Anthony	B-PERSON
Barrera	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
West	O
Nicolefurt	O
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Jordan	B-PERSON
Price	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
caches	O
in	O
Port	O
Robert.	O

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Kelly	B-PERSON
Friedman	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Williamfort	B-LOCATION
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Patrick	B-PERSON
Arnold	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Lake	O
Deniseview	O
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Lisachester	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Luis	B-PERSON
Guzman	B-PERSON
and	O
Brian	B-PERSON
Taylor	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
chemical	O
gas	O
near	O
Reedfort	B-LOCATION
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Gwendolyn	B-PERSON
Turner	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Marychester	B-LOCATION
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

03:00:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Matthew	B-PERSON
Blankenship	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
Nicholastown.	B-LOCATION

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Timothy	B-PERSON
Contreras	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
New	O
Karen	O
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Roger	B-PERSON
Hanson	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
North	O
Jennifer	O
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Desiree	B-PERSON
Medina	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Joshuachester	B-LOCATION
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Elizabeth	B-PERSON
Rose	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
New	O
Thomaston	O
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
East	O
Andrealand	O
just	O
after	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Goodmanland	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Scott	B-PERSON
Wilson	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
in	O
Andrewville	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Matthew	B-PERSON
Martinez	B-PERSON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Robert	B-PERSON
Gonzalez	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Ninaberg	B-LOCATION
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Amanda	B-PERSON
Williams	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
caches	O
in	O
Raymondbury.	B-LOCATION

Authorities	O
in	O
Jenniferchester	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Natalie	B-PERSON
Taylor	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Jamie	B-PERSON
Sullivan	B-PERSON
and	O
Barbara	B-PERSON
White	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
near	O
North	O
Donald	O
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

midnight:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Bonnie	B-PERSON
Scott	B-PERSON
transporting	O
drone	B-WEAPON
through	O
Collinsmouth.	B-LOCATION

dawn:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Robert	B-PERSON
Mcguire	B-PERSON
transporting	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
through	O
Port	O
Lindaside.	O

20:15:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Dawn	B-PERSON
Sanchez	B-PERSON
transporting	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
through	O
Toddmouth.	B-LOCATION

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
in	O
Nicholsfurt	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
John	B-PERSON
Allen	O
IV	B-PERSON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
Nathanville	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Sarah	B-PERSON
Aguilar	B-PERSON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

midnight:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Brianna	B-PERSON
Martin	O
DVM	B-PERSON
transporting	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
through	O
Port	O
Jeffreyview.	O

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Becky	B-PERSON
Lane	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
caches	O
in	O
Whitefurt.	B-LOCATION

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Felicia	B-PERSON
Powell	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
caches	O
in	O
New	O
Derekland.	O

Authorities	O
in	O
East	O
Markbury	O
detained	O
Jason	B-PERSON
Douglas	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Susan	B-PERSON
Mccarty	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
West	O
Valerieburgh	O
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Patrick	B-PERSON
Hubbard	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Stevenston	B-LOCATION
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Amanda	B-PERSON
Wagner	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Port	O
Stephenhaven	O
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Sonia	B-PERSON
Olsen	B-PERSON
and	O
Tina	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
drone	B-WEAPON
near	O
Thomasstad	B-LOCATION
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Sally	B-PERSON
Young	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
East	O
Ryanview	O
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Knightville	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Kelsey	B-PERSON
Munoz	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Meghan	B-PERSON
Reid	B-PERSON
and	O
Chad	B-PERSON
Arroyo	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
near	O
West	O
James	O
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
drone	B-WEAPON
in	O
Laurietown	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Kim	B-PERSON
Hunt	B-PERSON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
in	O
South	O
Bruceport	O
led	O
by	O
Christine	B-PERSON
Lopez	B-PERSON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Emma	B-PERSON
Brown	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Lake	O
Brendaland	O
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Brian	B-PERSON
Young	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Hodgehaven.	B-LOCATION

Misty	B-PERSON
Johnson	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Adamsmouth	B-LOCATION
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Davidborough	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Claudia	B-PERSON
Thompson	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Kayla	B-PERSON
Jackson	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
drone	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
South	O
Anna.	O

At	O
20:15,	B-TIME
Todd	B-PERSON
Case	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Casey	B-PERSON
Pugh	B-PERSON
in	O
East	O
Angela	O
to	O
discuss	O
RPG.	B-WEAPON

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Sarah	B-PERSON
Mcdonald	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Alyssamouth	B-LOCATION
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	B-WEAPON
carrying	O
drone	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Stanleybury	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
07:45.	B-TIME

John	B-PERSON
Wheeler	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
North	O
Shirleyfort	O
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Smithchester	B-LOCATION
detained	O
David	B-PERSON
Gonzalez	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
in	O
Ericaland	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
John	B-PERSON
Price	B-PERSON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
chemical	O
gas	O
in	O
Warrenton	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Nicole	B-PERSON
Clarke	B-PERSON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Allison	B-PERSON
Reyes	B-PERSON
and	O
Brandon	B-PERSON
Williams	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
drone	B-WEAPON
near	O
Andersonville	B-LOCATION
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Monica	B-PERSON
Velasquez	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
IED	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Sonyaborough.	B-LOCATION

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
in	O
Kaylaville	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Michelle	B-PERSON
Patel	B-PERSON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Bridget	B-PERSON
Kennedy	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
East	O
Travisland	O
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Debra	B-PERSON
Hernandez	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Brandonbury.	B-LOCATION

dawn:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Reginald	B-PERSON
Cruz	B-PERSON
transporting	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
through	O
North	O
Tannerstad.	O

20:15:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Joseph	B-PERSON
Jones	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
Kerrshire.	B-LOCATION

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Steven	B-PERSON
Hamilton	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
New	O
Jonathanville	O
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Timothy	B-PERSON
Gordon	B-PERSON
and	O
Stephanie	B-PERSON
Hunter	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
near	O
New	O
Barbaramouth	O
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
James	B-PERSON
Quinn	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
North	O
Lisaside	O
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	B-WEAPON
carrying	O
drone	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Matthewberg	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
West	O
Audrey	O
just	O
after	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Hilltown	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
IED	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Stevenberg	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
evening.	B-TIME

Jonathan	B-PERSON
Garcia	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Khanview	B-LOCATION
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Laura	B-PERSON
Murphy	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Brendaberg	B-LOCATION
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

At	O
20:15,	B-TIME
Amanda	B-PERSON
Lyons	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Rodney	B-PERSON
Collins	O
DVM	B-PERSON
in	O
West	O
Brandonberg	O
to	O
discuss	O
chemical	O
gas.	O

Collin	B-PERSON
Ho	B-PERSON
and	O
Mark	B-PERSON
Carpenter	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
IED	B-WEAPON
near	O
Port	O
Christopher	O
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Port	O
April	O
detained	O
Richard	B-PERSON
Boyd	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Gary	B-PERSON
Holmes	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Lynnstad	B-LOCATION
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Charlene	B-PERSON
Carlson	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Weberhaven	B-LOCATION
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Johnnyhaven	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Savannah	B-PERSON
Taylor	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Jaclyn	B-PERSON
Franklin	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
IED	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
West	O
Brandyland.	O

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
Blairfurt	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Michael	B-PERSON
Hull	B-PERSON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Smallmouth	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Deniseside	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Stephanie	B-PERSON
Henderson	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

07:45:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Douglas	B-PERSON
Gray	B-PERSON
transporting	O
IED	B-WEAPON
through	O
Savannahfurt.	B-LOCATION

Jillian	B-PERSON
Perez	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
North	O
Ariel	O
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Joanne	B-PERSON
Gibson	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
caches	O
in	O
New	O
Timothy.	O

07:45:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Ashley	B-PERSON
Hodge	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
New	O
Rodneyshire.	O

Daniel	B-PERSON
Lopez	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Stevenstad	B-LOCATION
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
North	O
Lisafort	O
detained	O
Lori	B-PERSON
Richardson	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Nicholas	B-PERSON
Lopez	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
East	O
Wandaton	O
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Christina	B-PERSON
Lee	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
South	O
Joseview.	O

Kelsey	B-PERSON
Clay	O
MD	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Scottland	B-LOCATION
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Larry	B-PERSON
Miller	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Caseyside	B-LOCATION
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Albert	B-PERSON
Moore	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Bradfordbury	B-LOCATION
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Edward	B-PERSON
Jones	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
caches	O
in	O
Coryville.	B-LOCATION

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
Erin	B-PERSON
Sims	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Ashley	B-PERSON
Johnson	B-PERSON
in	O
Williamsberg	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
sniper	O
rifle.	O

Melissa	B-PERSON
Simpson	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
East	O
Kayla	O
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Courtney	B-PERSON
Anderson	B-PERSON
transporting	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
through	O
Levinehaven.	B-LOCATION

Authorities	O
in	O
Hurstview	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Christopher	B-PERSON
Freeman	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Johnathan	B-PERSON
Mcclure	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
New	O
Madison.	O

Authorities	O
in	O
West	O
Christophermouth	O
detained	O
Cory	B-PERSON
Dorsey	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Andrew	B-PERSON
Brown	B-PERSON
and	O
Rebecca	B-PERSON
Garcia	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
near	O
Lake	O
Paul	O
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Paige	B-PERSON
Howard	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Chapmanfort	B-LOCATION
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Angela	B-PERSON
Kim	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Lake	O
Emilyfurt	O
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

At	O
07:45,	B-TIME
Susan	B-PERSON
Carter	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Emily	B-PERSON
Graham	B-PERSON
in	O
South	O
Theresa	O
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Joshua	B-PERSON
Malone	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
IED	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Franklinmouth.	B-LOCATION

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Anthony	B-PERSON
Jordan	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Daniellebury	B-LOCATION
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Dennis	B-PERSON
Martin	B-PERSON
and	O
Craig	B-PERSON
Vincent	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
near	O
Samuelport	B-LOCATION
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
Zoe	B-PERSON
Gates	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Shelby	B-PERSON
Gonzalez	B-PERSON
in	O
Michelleview	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
chemical	O
gas.	O

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Sandra	B-PERSON
Armstrong	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Jacobfort.	B-LOCATION

At	O
03:00,	B-TIME
Tyler	B-PERSON
Parker	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Nicolas	B-PERSON
Kim	B-PERSON
in	O
Stoneberg	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Bradfordberg	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
in	O
Christopherhaven	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Megan	B-PERSON
Campos	B-PERSON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
Kimberly	B-PERSON
Gonzales	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Daniel	B-PERSON
Valdez	B-PERSON
in	O
Christopherchester	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Peter	B-PERSON
Thompson	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
South	O
Travisview	O
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Teresa	B-PERSON
Pope	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Port	O
Raymondville	O
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Charles	B-PERSON
White	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
drone	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
South	O
Abigailtown.	O

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
chemical	O
gas	O
spotted	O
near	O
Lake	O
Amberfurt	O
just	O
after	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Port	O
Tonyafort	O
just	O
after	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Caitlyn	B-PERSON
Frye	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
East	O
Susan	O
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

07:45:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Carol	B-PERSON
Flores	B-PERSON
transporting	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
through	O
Lake	O
Timothy.	O

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Nicole	B-PERSON
Medina	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
chemical	O
gas	O
caches	O
in	O
Port	O
Julia.	O

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Adam	B-PERSON
Frey	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Jasonton.	B-LOCATION

Christopher	B-PERSON
Meyers	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Chandlerbury	B-LOCATION
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Deborah	B-PERSON
Jones	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Carterbury	B-LOCATION
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

dawn:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Timothy	B-PERSON
Singh	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
Cannonton.	B-LOCATION

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Andrew	B-PERSON
Gomez	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
New	O
Jasonhaven	O
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Amanda	B-PERSON
Daniel	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Franklinside	B-LOCATION
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Alexis	B-PERSON
Cardenas	B-PERSON
and	O
Stephanie	B-PERSON
Williams	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
near	O
North	O
Matthewville	O
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Jody	B-PERSON
Lambert	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Lake	O
Laura	O
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Michelle	B-PERSON
Ramirez	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Cruzborough	B-LOCATION
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Kristie	B-PERSON
Coleman	B-PERSON
and	O
John	B-PERSON
Wu	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
near	O
South	O
Tracybury	O
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Kathryn	B-PERSON
Garcia	B-PERSON
and	O
Derrick	B-PERSON
Moore	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
near	O
Herrerachester	B-LOCATION
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	B-WEAPON
carrying	O
drone	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Douglasmouth	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Mark	B-PERSON
Johnson	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
South	O
Alexshire	O
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Port	O
Amandaton	O
detained	O
Jay	B-PERSON
James	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Daniel	B-PERSON
Hanna	B-PERSON
and	O
Jacqueline	B-PERSON
Riley	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
near	O
Lake	O
Jenniferborough	O
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Jorgeland	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Dylan	B-PERSON
Jimenez	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Kellystad	B-LOCATION
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

20:15:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Eric	B-PERSON
Thornton	B-PERSON
transporting	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
through	O
New	O
Kelly.	O

At	O
evening,	B-TIME
Robert	B-PERSON
Ruiz	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Kevin	B-PERSON
Williams	B-PERSON
in	O
New	O
Brandonport	O
to	O
discuss	O
RPG.	B-WEAPON

Authorities	O
in	O
North	O
Tiffanyton	O
detained	O
Jacob	B-PERSON
Fuller	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
New	O
Susanchester	O
detained	O
Patricia	B-PERSON
Gardner	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Charlesside	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Joe	B-PERSON
Juarez	O
III	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Catherine	B-PERSON
Jackson	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
New	O
Holly	O
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
drone	B-WEAPON
in	O
West	O
Veronicafort	O
led	O
by	O
Lance	B-PERSON
Wyatt	B-PERSON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Ashley	B-PERSON
Reed	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
West	O
Dennisberg	O
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

20:15:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Patricia	B-PERSON
Montoya	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
Meyersstad.	B-LOCATION

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Jordan	B-PERSON
Tran	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
drone	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
East	O
Andreafort.	O

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Megan	B-PERSON
Blevins	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Cordovashire	B-LOCATION
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Amanda	B-PERSON
Mcdonald	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Port	O
Maria	O
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Rebecca	B-PERSON
Rodriguez	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
East	O
Scott	O
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Vanessa	B-PERSON
Ross	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Jensenview	B-LOCATION
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Stephanie	B-PERSON
Matthews	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
North	O
Chelsea	O
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Michael	B-PERSON
Barnes	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Myersfurt	B-LOCATION
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
West	O
Jenniferfurt	O
just	O
after	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Chase	B-PERSON
Green	B-PERSON
and	O
Brian	B-PERSON
Robertson	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
near	O
Wellschester	B-LOCATION
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Michael	B-PERSON
Jones	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Lake	O
Lisachester	O
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Cooperchester	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Scott	B-PERSON
Guzman	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Joshua	B-PERSON
Kramer	B-PERSON
transporting	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
through	O
North	O
Jennifer.	O

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Lee	B-PERSON
Aguirre	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Thomasmouth	B-LOCATION
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Lee	B-PERSON
Riley	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Jenniferborough	B-LOCATION
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
North	O
Lisaborough	O
just	O
after	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Haley	B-PERSON
Montes	B-PERSON
and	O
Jerome	B-PERSON
Powell	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
near	O
East	O
Jessica	O
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

13:30:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Steven	B-PERSON
Frye	B-PERSON
transporting	O
chemical	O
gas	O
through	O
North	O
Kenneth.	O

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
chemical	O
gas	O
in	O
North	O
Paulmouth	O
led	O
by	O
Jared	B-PERSON
Johnson	B-PERSON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
chemical	O
gas	O
spotted	O
near	O
East	O
Veronica	O
just	O
after	O
evening.	B-TIME

At	O
20:15,	B-TIME
Michael	B-PERSON
Williams	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
James	B-PERSON
Allen	B-PERSON
in	O
East	O
Cassandraview	O
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

Authorities	O
in	O
Brianside	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Jennifer	B-PERSON
Hughes	O
DVM	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

At	O
07:45,	B-TIME
Susan	B-PERSON
Ferguson	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Christian	B-PERSON
Hebert	B-PERSON
in	O
Jenniferview	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
RPG.	B-WEAPON

Authorities	O
in	O
Bentleyborough	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Amanda	B-PERSON
Hanson	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Andrea	B-PERSON
Huff	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
New	O
Diana	O
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
in	O
New	O
Rickyville	O
led	O
by	O
Curtis	B-PERSON
Rangel	B-PERSON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

At	O
07:45,	B-TIME
Martin	B-PERSON
Reese	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Michael	B-PERSON
Lewis	B-PERSON
in	O
Orozcostad	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

Angela	B-PERSON
Bernard	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Port	O
Davidberg	O
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Andrea	B-PERSON
Munoz	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
North	O
Jacobmouth	O
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Jennifer	B-PERSON
Rivera	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Mistyborough	B-LOCATION
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

At	O
13:30,	B-TIME
Sara	B-PERSON
Forbes	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Kyle	B-PERSON
Martinez	B-PERSON
in	O
New	O
Blake	O
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
drone	B-WEAPON
in	O
North	O
Diamond	O
led	O
by	O
Robert	B-PERSON
Snow	B-PERSON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
David	B-PERSON
Fox	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
South	O
Laura	O
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
IED	B-WEAPON
in	O
Lake	O
Angelborough	O
led	O
by	O
Denise	B-PERSON
Berry	B-PERSON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Port	O
Johnfort	B-PERSON
detained	O
Wesley	B-PERSON
Richardson	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Tinafurt	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Kayla	B-PERSON
Johnson	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Christina	B-PERSON
Ortiz	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
caches	O
in	O
Port	O
Deniseton.	O

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Joseph	B-PERSON
Morgan	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
South	O
David	O
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Vanessaville	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Nicole	B-PERSON
Hughes	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
New	O
Amanda	O
detained	O
Alex	B-PERSON
Hamilton	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

At	O
20:15,	B-TIME
Michael	B-PERSON
Shea	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Isaac	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
in	O
Lake	O
Williamborough	O
to	O
discuss	O
RPG.	B-WEAPON

Authorities	O
in	O
East	O
Mikayla	O
detained	O
Marco	B-PERSON
Wilson	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	B-WEAPON
carrying	O
drone	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Benitezmouth	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

midnight:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Ian	B-PERSON
Haynes	B-PERSON
transporting	O
IED	B-WEAPON
through	O
Hughesport.	B-LOCATION

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Dana	B-PERSON
Walker	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Scottmouth	B-LOCATION
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Matthew	B-PERSON
Harris	B-PERSON
and	O
Michele	B-PERSON
Mendoza	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
near	O
East	O
Steventon	O
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

At	O
03:00,	B-TIME
Sara	B-PERSON
Jackson	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Richard	B-PERSON
Delgado	B-PERSON
in	O
South	O
Veronica	O
to	O
discuss	O
grenade.	B-WEAPON

At	O
07:45,	B-TIME
Nicholas	B-PERSON
Spears	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Ashley	B-PERSON
Martin	B-PERSON
in	O
Halemouth	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

At	O
07:45,	B-TIME
Amanda	B-PERSON
Rodriguez	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Robert	B-PERSON
Johnson	B-PERSON
in	O
Kochland	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

Melanie	B-PERSON
Holmes	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Tracyburgh	B-LOCATION
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
North	O
Jeremiah	O
just	O
after	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Michael	B-PERSON
Bailey	B-PERSON
and	O
Nicholas	B-PERSON
Webb	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
drone	B-WEAPON
near	O
South	O
Emmaburgh	O
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
Port	O
Jameschester	O
led	O
by	O
Chad	B-PERSON
Owen	B-PERSON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Jonathan	B-PERSON
Johnson	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
North	O
Seanside	O
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

At	O
midnight,	B-TIME
Carmen	B-PERSON
Parrish	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Emily	B-PERSON
Ali	B-PERSON
in	O
Port	O
Edwardview	O
to	O
discuss	O
drone.	B-WEAPON

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Chris	B-PERSON
Young	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
West	O
Travis	O
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
South	O
Jimmy	O
detained	O
James	B-PERSON
Russell	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
Port	O
Erikstad	O
just	O
after	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
in	O
New	O
Samuel	O
led	O
by	O
Darlene	B-PERSON
Carter	B-PERSON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Scott	B-PERSON
Murray	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Robertsshire	B-LOCATION
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
North	O
Johnborough	O
detained	O
James	B-PERSON
Khan	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Julie	B-PERSON
Montoya	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Richardhaven	B-LOCATION
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
Daltonburgh	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Jonathan	B-PERSON
Brewer	B-PERSON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Lisa	B-PERSON
Dominguez	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
East	O
Melissaland	O
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Brian	B-PERSON
Landry	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Garyland	B-LOCATION
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Bradley	B-PERSON
Holt	B-PERSON
and	O
Bryan	B-PERSON
Wolfe	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
near	O
West	O
Michaelbury	O
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

At	O
13:30,	B-TIME
Michael	B-PERSON
Howard	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Theresa	B-PERSON
Rodriguez	B-PERSON
in	O
South	O
Zachary	O
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
chemical	O
gas	O
in	O
East	O
Robert	O
led	O
by	O
Jennifer	B-PERSON
Keller	B-PERSON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

At	O
midnight,	B-TIME
Melissa	B-PERSON
Kelly	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Ryan	B-PERSON
Williams	B-PERSON
in	O
Stevenhaven	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
sniper	O
rifle.	O

Authorities	O
in	O
Lake	O
Stephanie	O
detained	O
Robert	B-PERSON
Hutchinson	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

midnight:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Shawn	B-PERSON
Cortez	B-PERSON
transporting	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
through	O
Loveton.	B-LOCATION

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Nicole	B-PERSON
Drake	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Jamesborough	B-LOCATION
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

07:45:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Nathan	B-PERSON
Lester	B-PERSON
transporting	O
chemical	O
gas	O
through	O
Lake	O
Miguel.	O

Authorities	O
in	O
Gonzalezton	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Erin	B-PERSON
Ruiz	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
David	B-PERSON
Ortiz	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
South	O
Scottton.	O

Jenna	B-PERSON
Carlson	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Bauerfurt	B-LOCATION
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Ethan	B-PERSON
Palmer	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
East	O
Gregoryhaven	O
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Adamfurt	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
evening.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
in	O
North	O
Melissa	O
led	O
by	O
Heather	B-PERSON
Compton	B-PERSON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Amanda	B-PERSON
Harris	B-PERSON
transporting	O
IED	B-WEAPON
through	O
Williamburgh.	B-LOCATION

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Maria	B-PERSON
Bennett	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Torresfurt	B-LOCATION
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Brettmouth	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Angela	B-PERSON
Bautista	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
in	O
Port	O
Sean	O
led	O
by	O
Cody	B-PERSON
Torres	B-PERSON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Bethany	B-PERSON
Underwood	B-PERSON
and	O
Tammy	B-PERSON
Singh	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
near	O
Leeport	B-LOCATION
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Melody	B-PERSON
Jones	B-PERSON
and	O
Arthur	B-PERSON
Duke	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
chemical	O
gas	O
near	O
East	O
Joseph	O
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

At	O
20:15,	B-TIME
Christopher	B-PERSON
Clark	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Lisa	B-PERSON
Baker	B-PERSON
in	O
Schwartztown	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
chemical	O
gas.	O

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
James	B-PERSON
Murphy	B-PERSON
transporting	O
chemical	O
gas	O
through	O
Port	O
Christineport.	O

Sandra	B-PERSON
Hernandez	B-PERSON
and	O
Mary	B-PERSON
Mosley	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
chemical	O
gas	O
near	O
Port	O
Nancychester	O
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
Rodriguezburgh	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Kathleen	B-PERSON
Garcia	B-PERSON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Levi	B-PERSON
Hicks	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
IED	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Kimberlyberg.	B-LOCATION

Jason	B-PERSON
Sanchez	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
West	O
Nicole	O
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Mark	B-PERSON
Greene	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Amymouth	B-LOCATION
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
drone	B-WEAPON
in	O
Matthewview	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Heather	B-PERSON
Roberts	B-PERSON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
East	O
Seanfurt	O
just	O
after	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Adrienne	B-PERSON
Morris	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
North	O
Brandon	O
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Tiffany	B-PERSON
Allen	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
caches	O
in	O
Lake	O
Sandy.	O

Andrew	B-PERSON
Ware	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Lake	O
Jonathan	O
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
New	O
Kelsey	O
detained	O
Regina	B-PERSON
Fry	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

At	O
20:15,	B-TIME
Jessica	B-PERSON
Taylor	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Michael	B-PERSON
Byrd	B-PERSON
in	O
Bennettland	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
sniper	O
rifle.	O

Jessica	B-PERSON
Jacobs	B-PERSON
and	O
Katie	B-PERSON
Singh	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
near	O
Pedroshire	B-LOCATION
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
West	O
Jamesberg	O
just	O
after	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Monique	B-PERSON
Adams	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Port	O
Peterchester	O
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Ramirezmouth	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
midnight.	B-TIME

At	O
13:30,	B-TIME
Jennifer	B-PERSON
Holt	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Tami	B-PERSON
Rodriguez	O
DDS	B-PERSON
in	O
Rogersshire	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
RPG.	B-WEAPON

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Alex	B-PERSON
Valentine	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Sawyerborough	B-LOCATION
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

John	B-PERSON
Lane	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Port	O
Annette	O
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
South	O
Shawn	O
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
James	B-PERSON
Chung	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
New	O
Karenside	O
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Roberto	B-PERSON
Adkins	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
North	O
Edwinville	O
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Dr.	B-PERSON
Nathaniel	O
Brewer	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Acevedoshire	B-LOCATION
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

03:00:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Michele	B-PERSON
Miller	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
Harrisfurt.	B-LOCATION

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
John	B-PERSON
Jenkins	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Adam	B-PERSON
Anderson	B-PERSON
in	O
South	O
Emilyton	O
to	O
discuss	O
drone.	B-WEAPON

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
IED	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
South	O
Waynestad	O
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
West	O
Dominique	O
detained	O
Cory	B-PERSON
Cameron	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
IED	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Jodichester	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Leah	B-PERSON
Russo	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Port	O
Jeremystad	O
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
IED	B-WEAPON
in	O
Nashhaven	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Margaret	B-PERSON
Vang	B-PERSON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Alexis	B-PERSON
Ellis	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
South	O
Eric.	O

Devin	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
and	O
Michael	B-PERSON
Parker	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
IED	B-WEAPON
near	O
North	O
Frederick	O
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

At	O
03:00,	B-TIME
Nicholas	B-PERSON
Banks	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Christopher	B-PERSON
Valencia	B-PERSON
in	O
Port	O
Richard	O
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Jay	B-PERSON
Brown	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
chemical	O
gas	O
caches	O
in	O
North	O
Shane.	O

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
chemical	O
gas	O
spotted	O
near	O
Patriciaport	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
20:15.	B-TIME

dawn:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Anthony	B-PERSON
Miller	B-PERSON
transporting	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
through	O
Lake	O
April.	O

Kevin	B-PERSON
Graham	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
East	O
Christinaport	O
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
IED	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Port	O
Robert	O
just	O
after	O
evening.	B-TIME

Craig	B-PERSON
Ruiz	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Johnton	B-LOCATION
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Lisa	B-PERSON
Herrera	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Romerostad	B-LOCATION
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Watsonberg	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Carrie	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Glen	B-PERSON
Bradley	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
North	O
Jacob	O
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Port	O
William	O
detained	O
Dominique	B-PERSON
Price	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
IED	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Nicholsland	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
dawn.	B-TIME

At	O
13:30,	B-TIME
Kimberly	B-PERSON
Collins	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Craig	B-PERSON
Martinez	B-PERSON
in	O
South	O
Stephen	O
to	O
discuss	O
chemical	O
gas.	O

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
Crystal	B-PERSON
Schmidt	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Stephen	B-PERSON
Walker	B-PERSON
in	O
Martinton	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
chemical	O
gas.	O

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Mr.	B-PERSON
Marcus	O
Conner	O
Jr.	B-PERSON
transporting	O
IED	B-WEAPON
through	O
Macdonaldberg.	B-LOCATION

Mr.	B-PERSON
Seth	O
Cunningham	O
DVM	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Brianburgh	B-LOCATION
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Tyrone	B-PERSON
Ochoa	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Susanville	B-LOCATION
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Kayla	B-PERSON
Santana	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
IED	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
South	O
Christina.	O

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
chemical	O
gas	O
in	O
Amyberg	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Sherry	B-PERSON
Richards	B-PERSON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Jacqueline	B-PERSON
Wilson	B-PERSON
and	O
Adriana	B-PERSON
Thomas	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
near	O
Rossbury	B-LOCATION
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Cindy	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
East	O
Erikside	O
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
New	O
Sandra	O
just	O
after	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Seth	B-PERSON
Long	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Davenportfurt	B-LOCATION
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Port	O
Frederickmouth	O
detained	O
Chelsey	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Patricia	B-PERSON
Green	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Lake	O
Stephaniebury	O
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Christopher	B-PERSON
Stephenson	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Mcgeeview	B-LOCATION
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
North	O
Abigail	O
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Tiffany	B-PERSON
Martin	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
drone	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
South	O
Kimberly.	O

At	O
07:45,	B-TIME
April	B-PERSON
York	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Kevin	B-PERSON
Mccoy	B-PERSON
in	O
Pooleborough	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
grenade.	B-WEAPON

Katie	B-PERSON
Garner	B-PERSON
and	O
Mary	B-PERSON
Edwards	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
drone	B-WEAPON
near	O
Millerland	B-LOCATION
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Jonathan	B-PERSON
Allen	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Jordanburgh	B-LOCATION
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
North	O
Katiemouth	O
detained	O
Karen	B-PERSON
Velazquez	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Natalie	B-PERSON
Sawyer	B-PERSON
and	O
Joshua	B-PERSON
Daniel	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
near	O
Port	O
Heidihaven	O
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

03:00:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Jill	B-PERSON
Rogers	B-PERSON
transporting	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
through	O
South	O
Jason.	O

Deborah	B-PERSON
Thomas	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Robertsonfurt	B-LOCATION
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Kelly	B-PERSON
Marshall	O
DDS	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Lake	O
Williamburgh.	O

Authorities	O
in	O
Manuelview	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Kristina	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Mariah	B-PERSON
George	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
East	O
Bailey	O
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Daniel	B-PERSON
Campos	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
New	O
Michelleville	O
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Amanda	B-PERSON
Henderson	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Jenkinsmouth	B-LOCATION
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
in	O
New	O
Lauren	O
led	O
by	O
Roger	B-PERSON
Casey	B-PERSON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Jason	B-PERSON
Carpenter	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Michaelshire	B-LOCATION
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Joann	B-PERSON
Palmer	B-PERSON
transporting	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
through	O
Richardbury.	B-LOCATION

dawn:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Marcus	B-PERSON
Wallace	B-PERSON
transporting	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
through	O
New	O
Heather.	O

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
in	O
Claytonland	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Tricia	B-PERSON
Bell	B-PERSON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
chemical	O
gas	O
spotted	O
near	O
Perkinsland	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Frederick	B-PERSON
Schmidt	B-PERSON
and	O
Taylor	B-PERSON
Allen	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
near	O
Lake	O
Danachester	O
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
North	O
Daleview	O
just	O
after	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Maria	B-PERSON
Sanchez	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Steventon	B-LOCATION
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Paul	B-PERSON
May	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Nancyfort	B-LOCATION
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
in	O
Normanland	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Cheryl	B-PERSON
Davila	B-PERSON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	B-WEAPON
carrying	O
drone	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Joneschester	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Thomas	B-PERSON
Rodriguez	B-PERSON
and	O
Jonathan	B-PERSON
Marshall	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
near	O
Laurenland	B-LOCATION
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
drone	B-WEAPON
in	O
Lake	O
Victorfort	O
led	O
by	O
William	B-PERSON
Martinez	B-PERSON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
in	O
North	O
Katelyn	O
led	O
by	O
Hailey	B-PERSON
Daniels	B-PERSON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
IED	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Amyton	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
midnight.	B-TIME

07:45:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Katherine	B-PERSON
Stevens	B-PERSON
transporting	O
drone	B-WEAPON
through	O
Nguyenfort.	B-LOCATION

Authorities	O
in	O
South	O
Donald	O
detained	O
Alexander	B-PERSON
Rodriguez	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Barbara	B-PERSON
Green	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
chemical	O
gas	O
caches	O
in	O
Melissaport.	B-LOCATION

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Spencer	B-PERSON
Torres	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
South	O
Daniel.	O

Authorities	O
in	O
Newtonchester	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Kara	B-PERSON
Burns	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Timothy	B-PERSON
Porter	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Richardshire	B-LOCATION
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
IED	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Ramirezchester	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
midnight.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
David	B-PERSON
Sanders	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
drone	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Trevinomouth.	B-LOCATION

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
IED	B-WEAPON
in	O
South	O
Margaretview	O
led	O
by	O
Sherry	B-PERSON
Evans	B-PERSON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
North	O
Howard	O
detained	O
James	B-PERSON
Curtis	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
East	O
Lisa	O
just	O
after	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Bryce	B-PERSON
Payne	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
West	O
William	O
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Keith	B-PERSON
Rice	B-PERSON
and	O
Daniel	B-PERSON
Bradshaw	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
chemical	O
gas	O
near	O
Matthewfurt	B-LOCATION
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Sarah	B-PERSON
James	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Christinabury	B-LOCATION
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	B-WEAPON
carrying	O
drone	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
New	O
Brianfurt	O
just	O
after	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
West	O
Mistytown	O
detained	O
Ronald	B-PERSON
Watson	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
chemical	O
gas	O
in	O
South	O
Christian	O
led	O
by	O
Lindsey	B-PERSON
Velasquez	B-PERSON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Michael	B-PERSON
Garcia	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Butlerland.	B-LOCATION

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
IED	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Hallmouth	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

At	O
midnight,	B-TIME
Diana	B-PERSON
Mason	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Nicole	B-PERSON
Park	B-PERSON
in	O
New	O
Justin	O
to	O
discuss	O
AK-47.	B-WEAPON

Anna	B-PERSON
Ramos	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Taylorbury	B-LOCATION
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Christopher	B-PERSON
Edwards	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Hodgesside	B-LOCATION
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

03:00:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Michael	B-PERSON
Aguirre	B-PERSON
transporting	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
through	O
Warrenview.	B-LOCATION

Ashley	B-PERSON
Hopkins	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Rodneyborough	B-LOCATION
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
in	O
West	O
Victoria	O
led	O
by	O
Lori	B-PERSON
Nguyen	B-PERSON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Lauraberg	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
Brandonmouth	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Cindy	B-PERSON
Wells	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Markport	B-LOCATION
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Daniel	B-PERSON
Carlson	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Michaelfort	B-LOCATION
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

20:15:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Ryan	B-PERSON
Hoffman	B-PERSON
transporting	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
through	O
West	O
Travisview.	O

Crystal	B-PERSON
Russell	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Matthewton	B-LOCATION
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
Lake	O
Christian	O
just	O
after	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
New	O
Rickey	O
detained	O
Hunter	B-PERSON
Long	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
David	B-PERSON
Jackson	O
Jr.	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
IED	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Port	O
Matthew.	O

Michael	B-PERSON
Hancock	B-PERSON
and	O
Jessica	B-PERSON
Flores	O
MD	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
near	O
West	O
Charles	O
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
Washingtonbury	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Crystal	B-PERSON
Lang	B-PERSON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
North	O
Billton	O
just	O
after	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
West	O
Jermaineland	O
detained	O
Monique	B-PERSON
Clay	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Patrick	B-PERSON
Abbott	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
West	O
Christopher	O
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Mr.	B-PERSON
Joshua	O
King	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
East	O
Katherine	O
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Daniel	B-PERSON
Hartman	B-PERSON
and	O
Aaron	B-PERSON
Pollard	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
IED	B-WEAPON
near	O
Andreafurt	B-LOCATION
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Brendan	B-PERSON
Meza	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Shawnland	B-LOCATION
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

At	O
07:45,	B-TIME
Taylor	B-PERSON
Rivera	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Mr.	B-PERSON
Kyle	O
Williams	B-PERSON
in	O
East	O
Scott	O
to	O
discuss	O
grenade.	B-WEAPON

At	O
20:15,	B-TIME
Rhonda	B-PERSON
Cole	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Jessica	B-PERSON
Johnson	B-PERSON
in	O
Taylormouth	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
Carrville	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Larry	B-PERSON
Dunn	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
West	O
Markside	O
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Denise	B-PERSON
Cabrera	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Omarburgh	B-LOCATION
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Michael	B-PERSON
Avery	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Whiteburgh	B-LOCATION
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Robert	B-PERSON
Spencer	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Kennethburgh	B-LOCATION
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

At	O
07:45,	B-TIME
Kelly	B-PERSON
Robles	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Cory	B-PERSON
Brown	B-PERSON
in	O
North	O
Anthonyfurt	O
to	O
discuss	O
sniper	O
rifle.	O

dawn:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Carlos	B-PERSON
Mann	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
New	O
Kelsey.	O

dawn:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Jose	B-PERSON
Silva	B-PERSON
transporting	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
through	O
Olsonshire.	B-LOCATION

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
Michael	B-PERSON
Salinas	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Willie	B-PERSON
Spencer	B-PERSON
in	O
Cooperton	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
chemical	O
gas.	O

Authorities	O
in	O
Vanessafort	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Tracy	B-PERSON
Morris	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

13:30:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Karen	B-PERSON
Mills	B-PERSON
transporting	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
through	O
Susanstad.	B-LOCATION

At	O
20:15,	B-TIME
Erin	B-PERSON
Evans	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Jack	B-PERSON
Wolf	O
MD	B-PERSON
in	O
Grantborough	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

Allen	B-PERSON
May	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Port	O
Thomasport	O
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Christopher	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Danielmouth	B-LOCATION
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Aaron	B-PERSON
Brown	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
North	O
Keith.	O

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Michele	B-PERSON
Nolan	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Campbellchester.	B-LOCATION

Terry	B-PERSON
Soto	B-PERSON
and	O
Kara	B-PERSON
Pennington	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
near	O
East	O
Parker	O
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

At	O
07:45,	B-TIME
Charles	B-PERSON
Brown	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Clinton	B-PERSON
Morris	B-PERSON
in	O
Wardtown	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
sniper	O
rifle.	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
David	O
Davis	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
West	O
Edwardton	O
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Diane	B-PERSON
Wright	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Woodschester	B-LOCATION
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Salazarhaven	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Caitlin	B-PERSON
Moses	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Ellen	B-PERSON
Mccarty	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Mikaylaton	B-LOCATION
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

At	O
03:00,	B-TIME
Jose	B-PERSON
Edwards	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Garrett	B-PERSON
Delgado	B-PERSON
in	O
South	O
Janice	O
to	O
discuss	O
chemical	O
gas.	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Mallory	O
Thornton	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
East	O
Brandonhaven	O
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
East	O
Philipview	O
just	O
after	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Jamesview	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Sierra	B-PERSON
Johnston	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Courtney	B-PERSON
Farley	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
South	O
Karla	O
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Melissa	B-PERSON
Bullock	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Lake	O
Samanthafort	O
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Rebecca	B-PERSON
Walters	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Robinfurt	B-LOCATION
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Reedtown	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Nancy	B-PERSON
Sullivan	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
in	O
East	O
John	O
led	O
by	O
Renee	B-PERSON
Burgess	B-PERSON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Philip	B-PERSON
Bond	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
North	O
Andrewport	O
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
IED	B-WEAPON
in	O
South	O
Kyleshire	O
led	O
by	O
Colleen	B-PERSON
Brown	B-PERSON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
East	O
Jacobchester	O
just	O
after	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
Dianeton	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
in	O
Wendymouth	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Brooke	B-PERSON
Bradshaw	B-PERSON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Brian	B-PERSON
Hughes	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
North	O
Stanley	O
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

At	O
07:45,	B-TIME
Terry	B-PERSON
Prince	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Ashley	B-PERSON
Galloway	B-PERSON
in	O
Sydneyburgh	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
sniper	O
rifle.	O

Kathryn	B-PERSON
Rios	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
West	O
Brian	O
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
Jaime	B-PERSON
Mack	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Brittney	B-PERSON
Hughes	B-PERSON
in	O
Lake	O
Davidport	O
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

Maxwell	B-PERSON
Rosario	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Robertberg	B-LOCATION
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Middletonmouth	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Angel	B-PERSON
Nolan	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Port	O
Alan	O
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Leblancchester	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Mary	B-PERSON
Fowler	B-PERSON
and	O
Yolanda	B-PERSON
Clark	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
chemical	O
gas	O
near	O
Chadtown	B-LOCATION
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
Dillon	B-PERSON
Cantu	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Jennifer	B-PERSON
Lucas	B-PERSON
in	O
Lake	O
Erik	O
to	O
discuss	O
RPG.	B-WEAPON

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
drone	B-WEAPON
in	O
South	O
Richard	O
led	O
by	O
Kevin	B-PERSON
Wilkins	B-PERSON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Sean	B-PERSON
Anderson	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
IED	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
New	O
Kimberlyside.	O

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
East	O
Edwardmouth	O
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
New	O
Lawrence	O
detained	O
Phillip	B-PERSON
White	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
Sharon	B-PERSON
Murray	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Sandra	B-PERSON
Graves	B-PERSON
in	O
Levystad	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
RPG.	B-WEAPON

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
IED	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Paulaburgh	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Neilville	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Craig	B-PERSON
Summers	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
drone	B-WEAPON
in	O
North	O
Laura	O
led	O
by	O
Sandra	B-PERSON
Mosley	B-PERSON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Michael	B-PERSON
Brown	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
South	O
Christopherfurt	O
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Connie	B-PERSON
Palmer	B-PERSON
and	O
Brian	B-PERSON
Martin	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
chemical	O
gas	O
near	O
North	O
Angela	O
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

At	O
03:00,	B-TIME
Timothy	B-PERSON
Martinez	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Kelly	B-PERSON
Blake	B-PERSON
in	O
Lake	O
James	O
to	O
discuss	O
AK-47.	B-WEAPON

Tanya	B-PERSON
Taylor	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
New	O
Melindafurt	O
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Sandra	B-PERSON
Hall	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
IED	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
North	O
Jillbury.	O

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Kimberly	B-PERSON
Tate	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
New	O
Monicaland.	O

Veronica	B-PERSON
Rivera	B-PERSON
and	O
Mrs.	B-PERSON
Kelly	O
Reyes	O
PhD	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
near	O
North	O
Angelaville	O
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

George	B-PERSON
Schneider	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Paulshire	B-LOCATION
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
South	O
Billfort	O
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

midnight:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Kristin	B-PERSON
Brown	B-PERSON
transporting	O
IED	B-WEAPON
through	O
Jacksonmouth.	B-LOCATION

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Port	O
Heather	O
just	O
after	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
drone	B-WEAPON
in	O
Woodmouth	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Jacqueline	B-PERSON
Patterson	B-PERSON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Tiffany	B-PERSON
Rivera	B-PERSON
transporting	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
through	O
North	O
Crystalchester.	O

07:45:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Kimberly	B-PERSON
Wilson	B-PERSON
transporting	O
IED	B-WEAPON
through	O
Woodmouth.	B-LOCATION

07:45:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Maria	B-PERSON
Snow	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
Jeremyborough.	B-LOCATION

20:15:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Barbara	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
transporting	O
chemical	O
gas	O
through	O
South	O
Cherylstad.	O

Patrick	B-PERSON
Garcia	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Harmonbury	B-LOCATION
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
West	O
Eric	O
led	O
by	O
Jesse	B-PERSON
Ferguson	B-PERSON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
North	O
Timothy	O
detained	O
Austin	B-PERSON
Clark	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Eric	B-PERSON
Castillo	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
drone	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Johnstad.	B-LOCATION

Nicholas	B-PERSON
Sherman	B-PERSON
and	O
Douglas	B-PERSON
Taylor	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
drone	B-WEAPON
near	O
West	O
Jeremyville	O
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Derrick	B-PERSON
Ortega	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Jessicaport	B-LOCATION
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Christina	B-PERSON
Nunez	B-PERSON
and	O
Melody	B-PERSON
Fox	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
near	O
Bakerbury	B-LOCATION
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

At	O
20:15,	B-TIME
David	B-PERSON
Myers	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Robert	B-PERSON
Nelson	O
PhD	B-PERSON
in	O
Youngberg	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
AK-47.	B-WEAPON

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Veronica	B-PERSON
Robertson	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
South	O
Johnchester	O
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
in	O
Port	O
Dale	O
led	O
by	O
Kenneth	B-PERSON
Torres	B-PERSON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Scott	B-PERSON
Williams	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
drone	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
New	O
Alexandertown.	O

Michael	B-PERSON
Perez	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
East	O
Pennyburgh	O
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

07:45:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Carrie	B-PERSON
Reed	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
Millershire.	B-LOCATION

Steven	B-PERSON
Myers	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Parsonsburgh	B-LOCATION
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

13:30:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
John	B-PERSON
Terry	B-PERSON
transporting	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
through	O
New	O
Deborahmouth.	O

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
chemical	O
gas	O
spotted	O
near	O
Susanport	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Jennifer	B-PERSON
Johnson	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
IED	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
North	O
Brian.	O

Authorities	O
in	O
North	O
Gregory	O
detained	O
Tanya	B-PERSON
Ray	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
New	O
Lisa	O
detained	O
Michael	B-PERSON
King	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

At	O
07:45,	B-TIME
Kevin	B-PERSON
Brooks	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Michael	B-PERSON
Taylor	B-PERSON
in	O
North	O
Mary	O
to	O
discuss	O
AK-47.	B-WEAPON

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
Hendrickstown	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Jennifer	B-PERSON
Davidson	B-PERSON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Bruce	B-PERSON
Rocha	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
North	O
Ericfort	O
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Trevor	B-PERSON
Hill	B-PERSON
and	O
Sarah	B-PERSON
Maddox	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
near	O
South	O
Lisamouth	O
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Richard	B-PERSON
Davis	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Port	O
Natalieville	O
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
chemical	O
gas	O
in	O
Barberhaven	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Andrew	B-PERSON
Lopez	O
PhD	B-PERSON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

At	O
03:00,	B-TIME
Thomas	B-PERSON
Burns	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Michael	B-PERSON
Lee	B-PERSON
in	O
New	O
Patriciaburgh	O
to	O
discuss	O
RPG.	B-WEAPON

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
North	O
William	O
just	O
after	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Theodore	B-PERSON
Anderson	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
New	O
Travischester	O
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
Brownmouth	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Tammy	B-PERSON
Burns	B-PERSON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
Kimhaven	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Nicole	B-PERSON
Carrillo	B-PERSON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Josephshire	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Crystal	B-PERSON
Fry	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

midnight:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Brandy	B-PERSON
Martinez	B-PERSON
transporting	O
drone	B-WEAPON
through	O
North	O
Alexandra.	O

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Ashley	B-PERSON
Bolton	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Woodshire.	B-LOCATION

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
in	O
Lindaview	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Lisa	B-PERSON
Nelson	B-PERSON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Sallymouth	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Christopher	B-PERSON
Harrison	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
IED	B-WEAPON
in	O
Lake	O
Kathleen	O
led	O
by	O
Heather	B-PERSON
Mcintyre	B-PERSON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Latoya	B-PERSON
Hood	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
South	O
Perry.	O

Tyler	B-PERSON
Novak	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Cherylstad	B-LOCATION
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Wellsbury	B-LOCATION
detained	O
John	B-PERSON
Torres	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Patricia	B-PERSON
Edwards	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
North	O
Zachary	O
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

dawn:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Jamie	B-PERSON
Goodwin	B-PERSON
transporting	O
IED	B-WEAPON
through	O
Reginaport.	B-LOCATION

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Reyesbury	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
in	O
Patelbury	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Kylie	B-PERSON
Whitehead	B-PERSON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

midnight:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Edward	B-PERSON
Kelly	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
Harveystad.	B-LOCATION

midnight:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Kenneth	B-PERSON
Griffin	B-PERSON
transporting	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
through	O
West	O
Brittany.	O

20:15:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Jeffrey	B-PERSON
Pierce	B-PERSON
transporting	O
drone	B-WEAPON
through	O
Port	O
Amanda.	O

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
Ashley	B-PERSON
Barber	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Brooke	B-PERSON
Obrien	B-PERSON
in	O
Elizabethchester	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
sniper	O
rifle.	O

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
Michaelville	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
Williamsberg	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
20:15.	B-TIME

03:00:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Samantha	B-PERSON
Gonzales	B-PERSON
transporting	O
IED	B-WEAPON
through	O
Jeremytown.	B-LOCATION

Ian	B-PERSON
Brooks	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Melissatown	B-LOCATION
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Port	O
Brian	O
detained	O
Robin	B-PERSON
Meadows	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Jesus	B-PERSON
Bryan	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Oconnellhaven	B-LOCATION
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Katelyn	B-PERSON
English	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Sloanshire	B-LOCATION
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Kelly	B-PERSON
Swanson	B-PERSON
transporting	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
through	O
New	O
Richard.	O

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Angela	B-PERSON
Moreno	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Stephentown.	B-LOCATION

Melinda	B-PERSON
Sanford	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Lake	O
Susanport	O
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Michelle	B-PERSON
Young	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Thomasfort	B-LOCATION
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
Williamview	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Stephanie	B-PERSON
Nelson	B-PERSON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Nathaniel	B-PERSON
Wiley	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
East	O
Steventown	O
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

20:15:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Kimberly	B-PERSON
Sherman	B-PERSON
transporting	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
through	O
Dawnhaven.	B-LOCATION

Alex	B-PERSON
Garcia	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Port	O
Christineberg	O
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Stephanie	B-PERSON
Fitzpatrick	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Millerburgh	B-LOCATION
using	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

At	O
midnight,	B-TIME
Whitney	B-PERSON
Fowler	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Sharon	B-PERSON
Johnson	B-PERSON
in	O
Kristinamouth	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
grenade.	B-WEAPON

At	O
03:00,	B-TIME
Carol	B-PERSON
Bennett	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Margaret	B-PERSON
Lam	B-PERSON
in	O
Reynoldsburgh	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
RPG.	B-WEAPON

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Melinda	B-PERSON
Mccann	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Rogersport.	B-LOCATION

Authorities	O
in	O
Ryanland	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Rebecca	B-PERSON
Mercer	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Kristen	B-PERSON
Peterson	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
drone	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
Garyside.	B-LOCATION

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
in	O
Port	O
Kathleenfort	O
led	O
by	O
Kendra	B-PERSON
Guerra	B-PERSON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Sellersport	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Jordan	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
chemical	O
gas	O
in	O
Dennisland	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Caroline	B-PERSON
Baker	B-PERSON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
IED	B-WEAPON
in	O
Oconnorland	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Katie	B-PERSON
Phillips	B-PERSON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

20:15:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Elizabeth	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
transporting	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
through	O
Perezbury.	B-LOCATION

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
in	O
Williamsfort	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Tina	B-PERSON
Munoz	B-PERSON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
North	O
Deborahberg	O
detained	O
Amber	B-PERSON
Haas	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
chemical	O
gas	O
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
IED	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Lake	O
Elizabethland	O
just	O
after	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Phillip	B-PERSON
Stephens	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Markport	B-LOCATION
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Samantha	B-PERSON
Flores	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Port	O
Thomasmouth	O
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Elizabethmouth	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
evening.	B-TIME

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
Joe	B-PERSON
Lee	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Austin	B-PERSON
Erickson	B-PERSON
in	O
Lake	O
Allen	O
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
West	O
Patricia	O
just	O
after	O
evening.	B-TIME

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
David	B-PERSON
Rosales	B-PERSON
transporting	O
drone	B-WEAPON
through	O
Rodriguezhaven.	B-LOCATION

Charles	B-PERSON
Gonzalez	B-PERSON
and	O
Gary	B-PERSON
Barton	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
near	O
New	O
Jesse	O
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
Lindsayville	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Kyle	B-PERSON
Rhodes	B-PERSON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Tammy	B-PERSON
King	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Lindsayville	B-LOCATION
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	B-WEAPON
carrying	O
drone	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Sethton	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Richard	B-PERSON
Craig	B-PERSON
and	O
Valerie	B-PERSON
Molina	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
near	O
Sextonside	B-LOCATION
around	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
in	O
South	O
Amy	O
led	O
by	O
Kenneth	B-PERSON
Brennan	B-PERSON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

At	O
07:45,	B-TIME
Andrew	B-PERSON
Mclaughlin	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Kimberly	B-PERSON
Williams	B-PERSON
in	O
Michellehaven	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
RPG.	B-WEAPON

Karen	B-PERSON
Jackson	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Jasmineland	B-LOCATION
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Ronald	B-PERSON
Long	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Spenceville	B-LOCATION
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Nicole	B-PERSON
Richards	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
East	O
Thomas	O
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Eric	B-PERSON
Oliver	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
drone	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
West	O
Miranda.	O

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Michael	B-PERSON
Walls	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
chemical	O
gas	O
caches	O
in	O
Pamelaton.	B-LOCATION

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Lee	B-PERSON
Cruz	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
caches	O
in	O
Cruzberg.	B-PERSON

Authorities	O
in	O
Davisborough	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Victor	B-PERSON
Thompson	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Gregory	B-PERSON
Garcia	O
Jr.	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
drone	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
New	O
Nathaniel.	O

Stephen	B-PERSON
Fischer	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
West	O
Rebeccatown	O
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
drone	B-WEAPON
in	O
Garnerborough	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Amanda	B-PERSON
Rhodes	B-PERSON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Jeffrey	B-PERSON
Casey	B-PERSON
and	O
Dr.	B-PERSON
Rachel	O
Bowen	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
near	O
Atkinsfort	B-LOCATION
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
Murrayview	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
South	O
Johnmouth	O
led	O
by	O
Ryan	B-PERSON
Thompson	B-PERSON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Daniel	B-PERSON
Park	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Ramirezfurt	B-LOCATION
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	B-WEAPON
carrying	O
drone	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Timothyfort	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Daniel	B-PERSON
Long	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Westside	B-LOCATION
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Michelle	B-PERSON
Simmons	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Ronaldland	B-LOCATION
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Nicole	B-PERSON
Zhang	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
West	O
Mark	O
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Patrick	B-PERSON
Miller	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
New	O
Paul	O
using	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
North	O
Jennifer	O
led	O
by	O
Seth	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Katie	B-PERSON
Lowe	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
West	O
Jeffrey	O
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Maria	B-PERSON
Lopez	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
East	O
Deborahfurt	O
using	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
spotted	O
near	O
West	O
Scott	O
just	O
after	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
in	O
Ericaland	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-PERSON
Alyssa	O
Fuller	O
PhD	B-PERSON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

At	O
midnight,	B-TIME
Kelly	B-PERSON
Walker	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Susan	B-PERSON
King	B-PERSON
in	O
Wilkinshaven	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
chemical	O
gas.	O

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Justin	B-PERSON
Oneal	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
IED	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
East	O
Veronica.	O

Authorities	O
in	O
Geoffreyfort	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Phillip	B-PERSON
White	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Brian	B-PERSON
Hall	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
North	O
Davidmouth	O
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Nathan	B-PERSON
White	B-PERSON
and	O
Robert	B-PERSON
Phelps	O
DVM	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
near	O
Maxwelltown	B-LOCATION
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
IED	B-WEAPON
in	O
South	O
Pamelahaven	O
led	O
by	O
Kimberly	B-PERSON
Powell	B-PERSON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
chemical	O
gas	O
in	O
South	O
Reginaborough	O
led	O
by	O
Amanda	B-PERSON
Riley	B-PERSON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Timothy	B-PERSON
Hughes	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
West	O
Cheyenne	O
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Brian	B-PERSON
Fisher	B-PERSON
and	O
William	B-PERSON
Hamilton	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
near	O
Raymondborough	B-LOCATION
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

dawn:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Jennifer	B-PERSON
Ortega	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
East	O
Anthony.	O

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Claire	B-PERSON
Knox	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
South	O
Samuel	O
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
in	O
Haroldland	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Katie	B-PERSON
Williams	B-PERSON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Nathan	B-PERSON
Taylor	O
Jr.	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
South	O
Dylan	O
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Jeffrey	B-PERSON
Miller	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Port	O
Mark	O
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
IED	B-WEAPON
in	O
West	O
Ernest	O
led	O
by	O
Jennifer	B-PERSON
Mclaughlin	B-PERSON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Erin	B-PERSON
Garcia	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
drone	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
West	O
Roberthaven.	O

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Michael	B-PERSON
Hinton	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
chemical	O
gas	O
caches	O
in	O
Mercadoview.	B-LOCATION

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Daniel	B-PERSON
Brooks	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Simonhaven	B-LOCATION
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Nathan	B-PERSON
Elliott	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Sandraberg	B-LOCATION
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
13:30.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
in	O
Lake	O
Amanda	O
led	O
by	O
James	B-PERSON
Hodge	B-PERSON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
West	O
Evan	O
just	O
after	O
03:00.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Melanie	B-PERSON
Atkinson	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
caches	O
in	O
South	O
Danielbury.	O

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Marcus	B-PERSON
Brown	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
drone	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
East	O
Laurenborough.	O

Authorities	O
in	O
Williamsview	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Paul	B-PERSON
Nguyen	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
evening.	B-TIME

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
drone	B-WEAPON
in	O
Reedtown	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Jennifer	B-PERSON
Alvarado	B-PERSON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Alyssa	B-PERSON
Dunn	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Myerschester	B-LOCATION
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Tracy	B-PERSON
Stewart	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
East	O
Ryanmouth	O
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Amanda	B-PERSON
Peterson	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Josephmouth	B-LOCATION
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

Jessica	B-PERSON
Jackson	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
New	O
Cynthiaside	O
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

At	O
evening,	B-TIME
Patricia	B-PERSON
Stewart	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Reginald	B-PERSON
Oliver	B-PERSON
in	O
Christiefort	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
grenade.	B-WEAPON

Danny	B-PERSON
Harrison	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
Hortonfort	B-LOCATION
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Tracy	B-PERSON
Jacobson	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
East	O
Teresaburgh	O
using	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

evening:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Gary	B-PERSON
Diaz	B-PERSON
transporting	O
chemical	O
gas	O
through	O
New	O
Lindsaystad.	O

Phillip	B-PERSON
Curtis	B-PERSON
and	O
Lauren	B-PERSON
Gutierrez	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
chemical	O
gas	O
near	O
Camposchester	B-LOCATION
around	O
dawn.	B-TIME

20:15:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Savannah	B-PERSON
Henry	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
Jamesburgh.	B-LOCATION

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
in	O
Greenmouth	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Jason	B-PERSON
Craig	B-PERSON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
Steven	B-PERSON
Torres	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
Aaronburgh	B-LOCATION
using	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
dawn.	B-TIME

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
North	O
Martin	O
just	O
after	O
evening.	B-TIME

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
Jacob	B-PERSON
Smith	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Juan	B-PERSON
Yates	B-PERSON
in	O
Joseport	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
sniper	O
rifle.	O

Donald	B-PERSON
Torres	B-PERSON
and	O
James	B-PERSON
Dillon	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
drone	B-WEAPON
near	O
Ericport	B-LOCATION
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

At	O
evening,	B-TIME
Jordan	B-PERSON
Johnson	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Thomas	B-PERSON
Young	B-PERSON
in	O
Port	O
Antonio	O
to	O
discuss	O
sniper	O
rifle.	O

Multiple	O
drones	O
carrying	O
IED	B-WEAPON
spotted	O
near	O
Johnsonshire	B-LOCATION
just	O
after	O
07:45.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Courtney	B-PERSON
Young	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
caches	O
in	O
East	O
Joanview.	O

Devin	B-PERSON
Hardy	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
West	O
Stephenborough	O
around	O
03:00.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Mejialand	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Lisa	B-PERSON
Miller	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
07:45.	B-TIME

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
John	B-PERSON
Salazar	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Jonathan	B-PERSON
Evans	B-PERSON
in	O
New	O
Tammy	O
to	O
discuss	O
sniper	O
rifle.	O

Andrew	B-PERSON
Snyder	B-PERSON
and	O
Philip	B-PERSON
Hobbs	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
chemical	O
gas	O
near	O
Bethton	B-LOCATION
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Kelly	B-PERSON
Jenkins	B-PERSON
and	O
Terry	B-PERSON
Brown	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
near	O
North	O
Kristinaborough	O
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

13:30:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Mary	B-PERSON
Ponce	B-PERSON
transporting	O
chemical	O
gas	O
through	O
West	O
Samanthatown.	O

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
drone	B-WEAPON
in	O
Georgemouth	B-LOCATION
led	O
by	O
Deborah	B-PERSON
Rivera	B-PERSON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

At	O
dawn,	B-TIME
Darren	B-PERSON
Fitzgerald	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Joshua	B-PERSON
Eaton	B-PERSON
in	O
Leslieville	B-LOCATION
to	O
discuss	O
AK-47.	B-WEAPON

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
in	O
New	O
Deborah	O
led	O
by	O
Peter	B-PERSON
Kim	B-PERSON
at	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Military	O
sources	O
say	O
James	B-PERSON
Stuart	B-PERSON
planned	O
a	O
strike	O
at	O
East	O
Abigailstad	O
using	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
at	O
03:00.	B-TIME

At	O
20:15,	B-TIME
Mark	B-PERSON
Ferguson	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Jonathan	B-PERSON
Galvan	B-PERSON
in	O
East	O
Shannonview	O
to	O
discuss	O
IED.	B-WEAPON

Security	O
forces	O
responded	O
to	O
a	O
threat	O
involving	O
grenade	B-WEAPON
in	O
Lake	O
Larryport	O
led	O
by	O
Debra	B-PERSON
Horne	B-PERSON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Curtis	B-PERSON
Baker	B-PERSON
and	O
Vanessa	B-PERSON
Farrell	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
near	O
Port	O
Angela	O
around	O
13:30.	B-TIME

At	O
13:30,	B-TIME
Patrick	B-PERSON
Michael	B-PERSON
met	O
with	O
Melissa	B-PERSON
Gomez	B-PERSON
in	O
West	O
Christopher	O
to	O
discuss	O
drone.	B-WEAPON

Perry	B-PERSON
Pope	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Osbornestad	B-LOCATION
around	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Authorities	O
in	O
Vasquezfort	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Abigail	B-PERSON
James	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
AK-47	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Michael	B-PERSON
Skinner	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
caches	O
in	O
Mitchellchester.	B-LOCATION

A	O
joint	O
operation	O
led	O
by	O
Jerry	B-PERSON
Crawford	B-PERSON
uncovered	O
hidden	O
sniper	O
rifle	O
caches	O
in	O
Patelborough.	B-LOCATION

Authorities	O
in	O
Pattonland	B-LOCATION
detained	O
Mrs.	B-PERSON
Tina	O
Miller	B-PERSON
with	O
explosives	O
resembling	O
IED	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME

Joseph	B-PERSON
Murray	B-PERSON
and	O
Michael	B-PERSON
Adams	B-PERSON
conducted	O
a	O
drill	O
with	O
chemical	O
gas	O
near	O
North	O
Matthew	O
around	O
20:15.	B-TIME

Darrell	B-PERSON
Richards	B-PERSON
confirmed	O
a	O
suspicious	O
package	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Rogersview	B-LOCATION
around	O
evening.	B-TIME

dawn:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Bruce	B-PERSON
Marquez	B-PERSON
transporting	O
RPG	B-WEAPON
through	O
Deborahburgh.	B-LOCATION

03:00:	B-TIME
Surveillance	O
detected	O
Adam	B-PERSON
Maddox	B-PERSON
transporting	O
drone	B-WEAPON
through	O
Port	O
Stanleyport.	O

Regina	B-PERSON
Hooper	B-PERSON
warned	O
of	O
an	O
impending	O
attack	O
in	O
South	O
Mary	O
using	O
drone	B-WEAPON
at	O
midnight.	B-TIME
